Guide to the Levy Dime Novel Collection 1821-1968 Levy
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Monographic Series (Box 85-91)
  - Title: Bella's hero or; the Marquis & the freebooter A story of the Welch Marches Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 183 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 86, Folder 1751)
  - Title: Blackmail; or, the Countess Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 246 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 86, Folder 1752)
  - Author: Ross, Eric St.C. K. Title: By the queen's own hand. A true story of Lancashire life. Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 278 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 86, Folder 1753)
  - Title: Claire's love-life: a tale of English society. Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 134 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1754)
  - Author: Ross, Eric Title: Cliffroyal chase: or, loved by a Lancashire lad Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 188 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1755)
  - Author: Herbert, Bernard Title: The coastguard's daughter Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 274 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1756)
  - Author: Ashleigh, Rose (of South Carolina) Title: The condemned wife; or, the fatal secret A story of Jew and Gentile Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 190 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1757)
  - Author: L'Estrange, Captain W. D. Title: David Hartley's mistake; or, the mother's secret. A Yorkshire story Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 272 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1758)
  - Title: The dead witness: an American society novel Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 170 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1759)
  - Author: Payne, Charles G. Title: Desolate and opressed Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1760)
  - Author: Reade, Compton Title: The delasaux dilemma Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 242 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1761)
  - Author: Vaughn, Kate Title: Disappeared; or, the price of his silence Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 280 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1762)
  - Author: Ross, Eric Title: Doomed on the deep; or, life in Liverpool Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 147 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1763)
  - Author: McGregor, D. Title: The double secret Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1764)
  - Author: Phillips, Alfred R. Title: The Duke's daughter Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 142 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1765)
  - Author: Hanshew, T. W. Title: The Earl's secret Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 240 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1766)
  - Author: Calhoun, A. R. Title: Ella St. Clair, the child of the wreck Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 298 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1767)
  - Title: Even unto death; or, the mystery of the monk's tower Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 158 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1768)
  - Author: Strong, Hero Title: The favourite. A story of the stage Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 301 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1769)
  - Title: Felicia; or, a life-long feud. Also The sons of Schamyl Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 192 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1770)
  - Title: Fidelity: a tale of the reign of terror Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1771)
  - Title: A fool's advice; or, blundering Barney O'Hare Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1772)
  - Title: The golden gull; or, the mysterious seal Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 135 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1773)
  - Author: Ross, Eric Title: Grelley's money; or, a Manchester man's millions. The story of "The hundred years' will" Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1774)
  - Author: Phillips, Alfred R. Title: Held in a vice. A north of England story Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 250 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1775)
  - Author: Ashleigh, Rose Title: His other wife Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 153 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1776)
  - Author: L'Estrange, Captain W. D. Title: Jacob Ainsworth's gold. A Manchester story Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: [245] City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1777)
  - Title: The Jacobites; or, the highway mystery Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 187 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 87, Folder 1778)
  - Author: Major Victor Title: The king of the Dacoits. A romance of Burmah Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 247 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1779)
  - Title: Lady Cumberland's captivity Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 156 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1780)
  - Title: Lady Lilia; or, the blot on the escutcheon Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 186 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1781)
  - Author: Holland, S. Title: Lilian Lee; or, the lights and shadows of a girl's life Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 174 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1782)
  - Title: Living wages. A story of the great American strike Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 258 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1783)
  - Title: Lord Rory; or, the Lord of royal rest Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 199 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1784)
  - Title: Madeline; or, the forsaken bride Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 194 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1785)
  - Author: L'Estrange, Captain W. D. Title: The millionaire's ward. A story of Lancashire Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 300 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1786)
  - Author: Leys, John Title: The Moseley romance. As told by a lady ex-detective Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 337 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1787)
  - Author: Kingsley, C. Title: The mysterious jewel; or, the charge bequeathed from the sea Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 293 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1788)
  - Title: The mystery of Black-Tor lighthouse Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 268 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1789)
  - Title: Norma Norton's vow Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 248 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1790)
  - Title: O'Connor's child; or, the harp of the Innisfail Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 25 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1791)
  - Author: Richards, Hedley Title: The Omerod mystery Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 339 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1792)
  - Author: Ross, Eric StC. Title: Only a mill girl; or, a Manchester man's revenge Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 143 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1793)
  - Author: Villiers, Walter Title: Owen AP-Griffith Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 168 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1794)
  - Author: Brent, Enrest Title: Paul Davenant's niece Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 289 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1795)
  - Author: Greenwood, James Title: Pretty Lizzy Lisle Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 127 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1796)
  - Title: The pretty schemer; or, a husband well won Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 136 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1797)
  - Author: Whittaker, Captain Frederick Title: Princess Katrina: a story of love and war Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 295 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1798)
  - Title: The pride of race; or, the lost heir of the house of Linindale Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 109 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1799)
  - Title: The Roger Wilson case. A curious family history Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 162 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1800)
  - Title: Selma Wylde; or, marrying for revenge. An American society romance Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 178 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1801)
  - Author: Reade, Compton Title: Sowing and reaping; or, the county palatine of Chester Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 129 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 88, Folder 1802)
  - Author: Victor, Mrs. M. V. Title: To the very dregs Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 177 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1803)
  - Title: Trixy; or, the shadow of a crime Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 197 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1804)
  - Title: Two keys; or, Margaret Houghton's heroism Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 254 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1805)
  - Author: Vaughn, Kate Title: Under a cloud Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 251 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1806)
  - Title: The unwelcome guest; or, Lady Yune's enemy Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 130 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1807)
  - Author: Victor, Mrs. M. V. Title: The wages of sin Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 154 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1808)
  - Title: Walsinghame towers. A north-country story Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 307 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1809)
  - Title: The widow's wager: a tale of northern hearts & southern homes Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 138 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1810)
  - Author: Comfort, Lucy Randall Title: Wife and widow; or, the bride of the Alps Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 206 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1811)
  - Author: Victor, Mrs. Title: The wife's peril Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 161 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1812)
  - Author: Phillips, Alfred R. Title: Wild Darrel; or, the Earl's heir Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: [152] City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1813)
  - Title: A winter holiday; or the squire's party abroad. A romance of sunny lands Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 189 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1814)
  - Title: White Rudolph and Red Rudiger; or, the archers of the Alps Series Title: The People's Pocket Story Books Series Number: 182 City: London Publisher: James Henderson Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1815)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 1 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1816)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 2 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1816)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 3 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1816)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 4 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1816)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 5 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1816)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 6 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1817)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 7 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1817)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 8 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1817)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 9 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1817)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 10 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1817)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 11 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1818)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 12 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1818)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 13 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1818)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 14 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1818)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 15 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1818)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 16 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1819)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 17 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1819)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 18 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1819)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 19 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1819)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 20 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1819)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 21 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1820)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 22 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1820)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 23 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1820)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 24 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1820)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 25 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1820)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 26 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1821)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 27 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1821)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 28 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1821)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 29 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1821)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 30 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1821)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 31 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1822)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 32 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1822)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 33 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1822)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 34 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1822)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 35 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1822)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 36 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1823)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 37 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1823)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 38 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1823)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 39 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1823)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 40 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1823)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 41 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1824)
  - Title: Queen Draga or the regicide of Belgrade a sensational story of our own time Series Title: Premium Edition Series Number: 42 City: Springfield, Mass Publisher: The Springfield Guarantee Premium Company Date: undated (Box 89, Folder 1824)